Finding Aid for the W.W. Robinson papers, ca. 1843-1972
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Writings: arranged according to the Hicks bibliography.
  - Newspaper clippings., 1948, 1950, 1955, 1961 - 1962, and no date (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Captions for photographs., No dates; [4] leaves. Carbon typescript. (Box 38, Folder 42)
    San Fernando Valley - Calendar booklets - Publication material - A calendar of events
  - Janss Investment Co. Grand excursion to Owensmouth., 1912; 1 leaf. Printed flyer: Saturday December 7th, 1912, opening of the new electric railroad, monster free Spanish barbecue. (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Announcements., 1961, 1963, and no date (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Letters of appreciation., 1961, 1967, and no date; Includes letter from Robert D. Wayne. (Box 38, Folder 45)
    San Fernando Valley - Calendar booklets - Post - publication - A calendar of events
  - Reviews., 1951, 1961, and no date; Newspaper clippings. (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - 1 typescript leaf numbered 13., No dates; Similar to passages in both The story of San Fernando Valley and Fabulous San Fernando Valley. (Box 38, Folder 47)
    San Fernando Valley - Calendar booklets - Manuscript - A calendar of events
  - Letter from Lillian Stratton., 1967 Jul; 1 piece (letter). Encloses ms. concerning founding of the first motion picture studio in Culver City. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Culver City, California - Calendar booklets - Research material - A calendar of events - in which is included, also, the story of Palms and Playa del Rey together with Rancho La Ballona and Rancho Rincon de los Bueyes
  - Interviews about Playa del Rey, the lagoon, etc., No date (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Brochure., 1938 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings., 1937 - 1938, 1960, and 1967 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Review., 1939; Newspaper clipping. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Culver City, California - Calendar booklets - Post - publication - A calendar of events - in which is included, also, the story of Palms and Playa del Rey together with Rancho La Ballona and Rancho Rincon de los Bueyes
  - Historical flags of Orange County., No date (Box 39, Folder 6)
    The Old Spanish and Mexican Ranchos of Orange County - Calendar booklets - Research material.
  - Letter from J. Frank Dobie to Glen Dawson., 1951 Jan 16; 1 leaf. TLS. Ordering copy of The old Spanish and Mexican ranchos of Orange County. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    The Old Spanish and Mexican Ranchos of Orange County - Calendar booklets - Post - publication.
  - WWR's notes., No date; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    The Story of Tulare County and Visalia - Calendar booklets - Research material.
  - Letter from W.H. Allen., 1954 Feb; 1 piece. Encloses magazine clipping. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Magazines and journals., 1938, 1958, 1967, and 1969 - 1971 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - N.A. Huth - street map., 1948; City of Visalia and vicinity. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - No title., 1962 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    The Story of Tulare County and Visalia - Calendar booklets - Newspaper clipping.
  - Letter., 1952 Apr; 1 piece. Also 2 county centennial brochures. (Box 39, Folder 13)
    The Story of Tulare County and Visalia - Calendar booklets - Post - publication.
  - Biography of Alfred James Salisbury., 1927 Mar 18; 16 leaves. [Author unknown]. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 39, Folder 14)
    The Story of Ventura County - Calendar booklets - Research material.
  - Newspaper clippings., 1912, 1956 - 1958, 1960 - 1964, and 1966 - 1967 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence., 1955 Nov and 1956 Apr (Box 39, Folder 16)
    The Story of Ventura County - Calendar booklets - Publication material.
  - Reviews., 1956 Jan and May; Clippings. (Box 39, Folder 17)
    The Story of Ventura County - Calendar booklets - Post - publication.
  - Remarkable Captain Juan Wilson., No date; [5] leaves. [Author unknown]. Typescript. (Box 39, Folder 18)
    The Story of San Luis Obispo - Calendar booklets - Research material.
  - Newspaper clipping., 1957 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence., 1956 Apr and Dec; 5 pieces. Apr 1956 letter is a list of projects WWR thinks worthwhile during his retirement; letters also refer to San Bernardino and Riverside booklets. (Box 39, Folder 20)
    The Story of San Luis Obispo - Calendar booklets - Publication material.
  - WWR's notes on expenses., No date (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Letters of appreciation., 1957 May and 1960 Sep; 7 pieces. (Box 39, Folder 22)
    The Story of San Luis Obispo - Calendar booklets - Post - publication.
  - Reviews., 1957 Bun; Clipping. (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence., 1969 Jul; 4 pieces. Concerns permission to use WWR's work in another format. (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Letter., 1956 Mar; 1 piece. (Box 39, Folder 25)
    The Story of Riverside County - Calendar booklets - Research material.
  - Newspaper clippings., 1958 - 1960, 1963, 1968, 1970, and no date (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence., 1956 Bun and 1964 Mar; 2 pieces. (Box 39, Folder 27)
    The Story of Riverside County - Calendar booklets - Publication material.
  - Map (photocopy)., No date (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Announcement of autograph party. (Box 39, Folder 29)
    The Story of Riverside County - Calendar booklets - Post - publication.
  - Reviews., 1957 Bun - Jul and Sep; Clippings. (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Letter from Tom Patterson., 1969 Aug; 1 piece. (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence., 1957 Aug - Oct; 12 pieces. Enclosures with replies: Map of freeway progress, and Map of Mission Indian reservations. Includes letter from Patrice Manahan. (Box 39, Folder 32)
    The Story of San Bernardino - Calendar booklets - Research material.
  - WWR's notes., No date; 4 leaves. Holograph. (Box 39, Folder 33)
    The Story of San Bernardino County - Calendar booklets - Research material.
  - Map of the south - west portion of San Bernardino County, embracing 48 townships., No date; Photocopy. (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Printed and mimeographed material., 1938, 1957, 1960, and no date (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Newspaper clipping., 1959 - 1960, 1966 - 1967, and no date (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Clipping, Location notice, and real estate document [photocopies]., 1888, 1905, and 1949; Location notice, quartz claim. Real estate document of Virgil Earp. (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence., 1958 Mar - May, and no date; 22 pieces. Requests to read manuscript and suggestions received. Includes letters from: L. Burr Beldon, George Whitney. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    The Story of San Bernardino County - Calendar booklets - Manuscript material.
  - Correspondence., 1957 Sep, 1958 Feb, and no date; 10 pieces. Concerning map in book. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    The Story of San Bernardino County - Calendar booklets - Publication material.
  - Correspondence., 1957 Nov and no date; 4 pieces. Printer's estimate, quotations for publicity, etc. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Announcements., 1959 Apr - May (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Letters of congratulation and appreciation., 1959 Apr - May; 9 pieces. Letters from: Carey S. Bliss, Dwight L. Clarke, J. Frank Dobie, Francis Farquhar, Marcus Crahan, David Magee. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    The Story of San Bernardino County - Calendar booklets - Post - publication.
  - Letters requesting copies., 1959 May and 1971 Dec; 3 pieces. Includes letter from: Larry E. Burgess. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Reviews., 1959 Apr - May; Newspaper and magazine clippings. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Kern County notes, memos, etc. (aftermath of a booklet)., No dates (Box 40, Folder 8)
    The Story of Kern County - Calendar booklets - WWR's filing note.
  - Letters requesting research material and replies., 1960 Dec and 1961 Jan - Feb; 14 pieces. With enclosures. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    The Story of Kern County - Calendar booklets - Research material.
  - WWR's notes., No date; 104 leaves. Holograph. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Printed items., 1894, 1950, 1955 - 1957, 1959, 1963 - 1964, and no date; 13 pieces. Primarily from the Kern County Historical Society. Includes the cost of making a settler's home in the famous Kern delta. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Maps. f.1 of 3., 1952; U.S.D.A. Forest Service, Sequoia National Forest (south half), Mt. Diablo Meridian. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Maps. f.2 of 3., 1953; Maps - U.S.D.A. Forest Service, National forests of California, f. 2 of 3. (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Maps. f.3 of 3., 1957; Map of Kern County adapted from the general county map as judicial districts. Prepared and issued by Bakersfield Abstract Division, TIT. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Magazine and newspaper clippings., 1950, 1952 - 1953, 1961 - 1962, 1965, and no date (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - The story of Kern County., 1961; 52 leaves. Typescript (carbon). Sent to George L. Henderson, for comment. Includes letter to WWR from GLH, Feb 1961. (Box 40, Folder 16)
    The Story of Kern County - Calendar booklets - Manuscripts.
  - The story of Kern County., 1961; [14] leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections. Section headed "1936: a corporation takes over " to the end of the work. (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence., 1960 Dec; 4 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 18)
    The Story of Kern County - Calendar booklets - Publication material.
  - The story of Kern County., 1961; 55 leaves. Typescript and carbon typescript with holograph and paste-on corrections. Printer's copy. (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - The story of Kern County., 1961; 23 leaves. Uncorrected galley proofs. (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - The story of Kern County., 1961; 23 leaves. Corrected galley proofs. Together with 1 leaf: new corrections. (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Letters of appreciation, etc., 1961 Apr, and 1963 Jan Mar (Box 40, Folder 22)
    The Story of Kern County - Calendar booklets - Post - publication.
  - Reviews., 1961 Mar - Apr; Newspaper clipping. (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - WWR's list of recipients., No date; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - As distributed the following dates., 1935, 1942, 1948, 1954, 1957, 1961, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Land Titles in Long Beach - Calendar booklets - Copies.
  - As distributed the following dates., 1935, 1942, 1950 (anniversary edition), 1950, 1955, 1959, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Santa Monica - Calendar booklets - Copies - A calendar of events that made a city
  - As distributed the following dates., 1935, 1942, 1949, 1955, 1961, 1964; 1942 - holograph corrections (apricot), 1949 - 2 copies (1 orange, 1 rust cover), 1955 - 2 copies. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Pasadena - Calendar booklets - Copies - A calendar of events in the making of a city
  - As distributed the following dates., 1935, 1942, 1947, 1955, 1957, 1961, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    Whittier - Calendar booklets - Copies - A calendar of events in the making of a city
  - As distributed the following dates., 1936, 1942; 1942 - holograph corrections. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    Glendale - Calendar booklets - Copies - A calendar of events in the making of a city
  - As distributed the following dates., 1936, 1936 (gold cover), 1942 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    Monrovia - Calendar booklets - Copies - A calendar of events in the making of a city
  - As distributed the following dates., 1936, 1942; 1936 - 2 copies. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Pomona - Calendar booklets - Copies - A calendar of events in the making of a city
  - As distributed the following dates., 1937, 1942 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    San Pedro and Wilmington - Calendar booklets - Copies - A calendar of events in the making of two cities and the Los Angeles Harbor
  - As distributed the following dates., 1937, 1942, 1947, 1955, 1958, 1962, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    Inglewood - Calendar booklets - Copies - A calendar of events in the making of a city
  - As distributed the following dates., 1938, 1942 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    Beverly Hills - Calendar booklets - Copies - A calendar of events in the making of a city
  - As distributed the following dates., 1938, 1942, 1951, 1961, 1964, 1967; Revised and reprinted as The story of San Fernando Valley for 1961 and after, 1951 - 2 copies, 1967 - 2 copies. (Box 41, Folder 11)
    San Fernando Valley - Calendar booklets - A calendar of events
  - As distributed the following dates., 1939, 1942 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    Culver City - Calendar booklets - Copies - A calendar of events - in which is included, also, the story of Palms and Playa Del Rey together with Rancho La Ballona and Rancho Rincon de los Bueyes
  - As distributed the following dates. f.1 of 2., 1950, 1952, 1953, 1954, 1955; 1952 - 2 copies. (Box 41, Folder 13)
    The Old Spanish and Mexican Ranchos of Orange County - Calendar booklets - Copies.
  - As distributed the following dates. f.2 of 2., 1956, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1965; 1956 - 2 copies. (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - As distributed the following dates., 1952, 1955, 1958, 1960, 1962, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    The Story of Tulare County and Visalia - Calendar booklets - Copies.
  - As distributed the following dates., 1955, 1956, 1957, 1963; 1963 - 2 copies. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    The Story of Ventura County - Calendar booklets - Copies.
  - As distributed the following dates., 1957, 1960, 1962, 1964, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    The Story of San Luis Obispo County - Calendar booklets - Copies.
  - As distributed the following dates., 1957, 1959, 1964; 1957 - 2 copies, 1964 - not here. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    The Story of Riverside County - Calendar booklets - Copies.
  - As distributed the following dates., 1958, 1959, 1962, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    The Story of San Bernardino County - Calendar booklets - Copies.
  - As distributed the following dates., 1961, 1963, 1965; 1961 - 2 copies. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    The Story of Kern County - Calendar booklets - Copies.
  - Announcement., 1954?; Card with W. Herbert Allen's signature (printed). (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Titles - Compiled and edited works - Post - publication - A practical manual of California land law for title and trust companies, banks and interested laymen; of forms for title men; and of legal terms and phrases
  - Certificate of copyright., 1942 Feb (Box 43, Folder 2)
    What They Say About the Angels - Compiled and edited works - Publication material.
  - Letter from Charles Yale., 1943 Jan 5; 1 piece. TPS. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    What They Say About the Angels - Compiled and edited works - Post - publication.
  - Letters of appreciation., 1942 Feb - May, and no date; 10 pieces. Some enclose copies of reviews, etc. Includes letter from: Archbold Robinson. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Letter from Faith Holmes Byers., 1942 Mar; 1 piece. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Script for: Looks at books by Faith Holmes Byers., 1942 April 29; [8] leaves. KFI, Sundays at 12:45 p.m. Typescript with holograph corrections. Includes dialogue marked "Robinson". (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Reviews., 1941 Sep, 1942 Feb - Mar, and no date; Clippings. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Copy of the book with individual quotations pasted on note cards., No dates; 79 cards. Cards often with additional notes by WWR. Possibly intended for use in lectures?. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence., 1946 Oct and Dec; 5 pieces. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    T 'N' T - Compiled and edited works - Research material - A monthly company magazine published by Title Insurance and Trust Company
  - Collection of oddities by W.W. Robinson., No dates; Scrapbook with "filler" items for the publication. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Copies., 1946 Dec and 1947 Jan; V.2, no.11; V.3, no.1. News of WWR mentioned in Jan 1947 issue. Both contains articles on history of T.I.T. Article in Dec 1946 issue. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    T 'N' T - Compiled and edited works - Publication material - A monthly company magazine published by Title Insurance and Trust Company
  - WWR article., 1956 May; v.12 no.5. Connie Riebe needs no introduction, says W.W.R., but--. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Mention., 1951 May; Newspaper clipping. (Box 43, Folder 13)
    T 'N' T - Compiled and edited works - Post - publication - A monthly company magazine published by Title Insurance and Trust Company
  - Correspondence, f.1 of 2., 1946 Jul, Dec, 1947 Jan - Mar, Jul and Dec, 1948 May, Nov; Letters from: Charles K. Adams, Carl Wheat, Andre Simon, Marcus Crahan. (Box 43, Folder 14)
    Hoja Volante - Compiled and edited works - Research material - A quarterly published by the Zamorano Club, Los Angeles
  - Correspondence, f.2 of 2., 1949 Jan, Apr, Aug, Oct, 1950 Oct. 1953 Nov, 1954 Mar, no date; Letters from: Charles K. Adams, Marcus Crahan, Francis P. Farquhar, Frederick Webb Hodge, Willis Kerr, H. Richard Archer, and Lawrence Clark Powell. (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - WWR's notes., No dates; 44 leaves. Typescript and (primarily) holograph. (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Magazine clippings, printed and mimeographed materials., 1927 - 1971 (inclusive); Dates are primarily 1950s. (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings., 1946, 1953 - 1958, 1966, 1971 - 1972, and no date; Initially collected for news notes on Zamorano members. (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Various paragraphs, drafts for the publication., No dates; 16 leaves. Holograph. (Box 43, Folder 19)
    Hoja Volante - Compiled and edited works - Manuscript material - A quarterly published by the Zamorano Club, Los Angeles
  - Typescript for WWR's first issue as editor., No date; 5 leaves. Incomplete. (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Typescripts, first issue and others., Various dates; 41 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Hoja volante. no.15., 1947 May; 6 leaves. Page proofs with corrections. (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Hoja volante., 1950 Nov; 1 leaf. Page proof with corrections. Incomplete. (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Hoja volante. no.15, 21, 24., No date; With minor holograph markings by WWR. (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Letters of appreciation., 1948 Feb, May, and 1950 May, Aug, Nov; 7 pieces. Letters from: Charles K. Adams, Idwal Jones. (Box 43, Folder 25)
    Hoja Volante - Compiled and edited works - Post - publication - A quarterly published by the Zamorano Club, Los Angeles
  - Letter., 1951 Jan; Accepting WWR's resignation. (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Letter of appreciation., 1958 Jan (Box 43, Folder 27)
    The Westerners Brand Book - Compiled and edited works - Post - publication - Book number seven
  - Letter., 1965 Aug; Encloses photocopy of poem. (Box 43, Folder 28)
    San Francisco and Los Angeles in 1884 - Compiled and edited works - Post - publication.
  - Bookseller's catalog., 1962 Mar; Listing in: Yale Brown, booksellers, catalogue 40. (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Letter., 1937 [sic, 1967?] Feb 6 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Reviews., 1961 May Jul, and no date; Clippings. (Box 43, Folder 31)
    A Bookman's View of Los Angeles - Compiled and edited works - Post - publication.
  - Letter from Tyrus G. Harmsen., 1965 Dec; 1 piece. (Box 43, Folder 32)
    Zamorano Choice - Compiled and edited works - Research material - Selections from the Zamorano Club's "Hoja volante" 1934 - 1966
  - Notes by WWR., No date; 6 leaves. Holograph. (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence., 1967 Feb - Mar; 8 pieces. Concerns copyright. (Box 43, Folder 34)
    Zamorano Choice - Compiled and edited works - Publication material - Selections from the Zamorano Club's "Hoja volante" 1934 - 1966
  - WWR's notes., No date; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 43, Folder 35)
    Sixty Years in Southern California, 1853 - 1913 - Compiled and edited works - Research material - Containing the reminiscences or Harris Newmark (Fourth edition)
  - Newspaper clipping., No date (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Letter from Grover Jacoby., 1970 Mar; 2 pieces. From relative of Newmark. (Box 43, Folder 37)
    Sixty Years in Southern California, 1853 - 1913 - Compiled and edited works - Post - publication - Containing the reminiscences or Harris Newmark (Fourth edition)
  - List of books by Irene and W W Robinson., 1946?; 1 leaf. Holograph. In IBR's hand on California Water Color Society letterhead. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    More Than One Title - Juvenile books - Bibliography.
  - Notes., No date; 2 leaves. Holograph. In WWR's hand. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    More Than One Title - Juvenile books - Research material.
  - Clippings., 1935, 1965, and no date (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence. f.1 of 2., 1939 Jul, 1938 Jul, 1940 Jan, 1954 Jul, 1962 Nov, and 1963 Sep (Box 44, Folder 4)
    More Than One Title - Juvenile books - Post - publication.
  - Correspondence. f.2 of 2., 1964 Jan, 1967 Feb - Mar, 1968 Dec, and no date (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Letter from Irvine Kerlan., 1959 Apr 15; 1 item, 2 pieces. And enclosures. Enclosures about Kerlan and his collection. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - WWR's notes for talk., No date; 5 leaves. Holograph and typescript with holograph corrections. Seems to be structured around Lions. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Publisher's announcements., 1963, 1965 - 1966, 1968 - 1969 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Bryson, Frances Wood. Irene and W.W. Robinson., 1937 Jul - Aug; In: the horn book magazine, books and reading for young people. v.13 no.4. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Reviews and mentions, more than one title., 1938 - 1939 and 1941; Magazine clippings. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Reviews and mentions., 1938 Nov and 1940 Dec; Clippings of articles by Perry Worden. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Author appearances. Newspaper clippings., 1962 Oct - Nov and 1965 Oct (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Author appearances. Programs., 1950 Jul, 1962 Dec, 1963 Nov, and no date (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Items collected about children's literature., 1955 - 1956 and no date; No mentions of IBR or WWR. (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Publishers' announcements and booksellers' catalogs., 1932, 1961, and no date (Box 44, Folder 15)
    Beasts of the Tar Pits - Juvenile books - Publication material - Tales of ancient America
  - Reviews., 1932 Jul - Sep and Nov, 1933 Feb, 1941 Jul, and no date; Clippings and photocopies of clippings. (Box 44, Folder 16)
    Beasts of the Tar Pits - Juvenile books - Post - publication - Tales of ancient America
  - Correspondence., 1933 Jul - Aug, 1934 Jul, 1935 Jul, and 1958 Mar; 6 pieces. 4 items, 5 pieces. 1 piece. Also WWR's notes on envelope. (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence., 1934 Jul and 1935 Jul; 2 items, 5 pieces. Royalty statements. (Box 44, Folder 18)
    Ancient Animals - Juvenile books - Post - publication.
  - Publisher's announcements., 1966 - 1967 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Reviews., 1934 May Aug, 1962 Aug, and no date; Clippings and photocopies of clippings. (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence., 1934 Jan, Feb and Sep, and 1965 Apr; 4 items, 5 pieces. 1934 photocopies. (Box 44, Folder 21)
    Animals in the Sun - Juvenile books - Publication material - About crocodiles, lizards, turtles and snakes
  - Reviews., 1934 Oct - Dec; Clippings and photocopies of clippings. (Box 44, Folder 22)
    Animals in the Sun - Juvenile books - Post - publication - About crocodiles, lizards, turtles and snakes
  - Publishers' announcements., 1962, 1964, and no date (Box 44, Folder 23)
    Elephants - Juvenile books - Publication material.
  - Correspondence., 1941 May, 1962 Mar and 1968 Aug; 4 items, 4 pieces. (Box 44, Folder 24)
    Elephants - Juvenile books - Post - publication.
  - Reviews., 1935 Nov - Dec, 1936 Feb, and 1937 Nov; Clippings and photocopies of clippings. (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Form, permission to reprint., 1967 Feb (Box 44, Folder 26)
    Lions - Juvenile books - Post - publication.
  - Reviews., 1936 Nov - Dec, and 1937 Jan - Mar Bun; Clippings and photocopies of clippings. (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Mention., 1950 Mar; Magazine clippings. (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Announcement., 1966 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    The Book of Bible Animals - Juvenile books - Publication material.
  - Dust jacket., 1966; [2 copies]. (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Letter., 1966 Aug, Nov; 2 items, 2 pieces. (Box 44, Folder 31)
    The Book of Bible Animals - Juvenile books - Post - publication.
  - Reviews., 1938 Sep, Nov - Dec; 1939 Mar, Bun - Jul, Sep; 1965 Oct; 1967 Feb; no date; Newspaper clippings. (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Author appearance. Clippings., 1967 Jan (Box 44, Folder 33)